<package>
	<id>apktw.org.hacx.callrecorder</id>
	<name>Call Recorder (iOS)</name>
  <name>（已破解DRM）</name>
	<version>2.07-3</version>
	<compatibility>
		<firmware>
			<miniOS>6.0</miniOS>
		</firmware>
	</compatibility>
	<dependencies>
    <package>firmware (>= 6.0)</package>
		<package>mobilesubstrate</package>
		<package>applist</package>
		<package>org.hacx.hacxdaemon</package>
	</dependencies>
	<descriptionlist>
		<description><![CDATA[
<font color='red'>Compatible with iPhone 4S/5/5C/5S/6/6+/6S/6S+ on iOS 7.0 - 9.02</font><br />
      <br />
Record any Phone Call or VoIP Call (speaker or microphone, except iPhone 4S) on your device without using an external call service.<br />
<br />
Supports: Phone/Voip Calls, Viber, Skype, FaceTime, Line, Music App, YouTube, Spotify, Radio, etc,..<br />
<br />
<p style='text-align: center; font-size:15px;'>
Call Recorder App: Play/Delete/Share your recordings and quickly setup Activator gestures.<br />
<br />
Internal Web Server allows to easily access all your recordings from your personal computer and directly download, delete or play them from the device.<br />
<br />
Skype/Viber &amp; CallBar Support: Adds a quick record button directly into the call view.<br />
<br />
Google Drive: Every recording will be automatically uploaded to your Google Drive account when you finish recording.<br />
<br />
Activator Support: Toggle recording by Triple clicking the home button (or set other Activator gesture from the inside the application settings).<br /></p>
    ]]></description>
    <description><![CDATA[
* This tweak only works on iPhone 4S/5/5C/5S/6/6+/6S/6S+ with iOS 7 and up.<br />
on iPhone 4S it only works while playing through the external Speaker.<br />
<br />
** In some countries it's illegal to perform a recording without the other party acknowledgement. Call Recorder can play a beep sound every 20 seconds to notify the other party of a recording taking place (You can disable/enable beeping from the application). Yaniv Danan (aka @hAcx) cannot be held responsible for any illegal use of this application and by installing this application you confirm that you take full responsibility on actions performed by this application **<br />
    ]]></description>
	</descriptionlist>
	<screenshots>
		<screenshot>
			<description></description>
			<image></image>
		</screenshot>
	</screenshots>
	<changelog>
		<change>Even more iOS 9 Support</change>
    <change>Fixed - "Add Contact" in auto record settings was not working</change>
    <change>Fixed - Settings not saved</change>
	</changelog>
	<links>
		<link>
			<name>APK.TW 台灣中文網</name>
			<url>http://apk.tw/</url>
		</link>
	</links>
</package>