<changelog>
  <changes>
		<version>7.5.1</version>
		<change><![CDATA[
Features:<br />
+ Added 3D Touch app shortcuts (for registered devices, enable in settings).<br />
    ]]></change>
		<change><![CDATA[
Fixes and improvements:<br />
* Replaced "Reset" button with "All" button in the excluded apps menus.<br />
* Improved the keyboard removal tool on iOS 9.x (it's now able to clear hundreds of megabytes on the root filesystem).<br />
* Improved small icon for better display in the app switcher.<br />
* Adopted San Francisco font on cleanup view in iOS 9.<br />
* Added Portuguese (Portugal) localization.<br />
* Temporarily removed IconBundles support in iOS 9.x, will be reintroduced whenever IconBundles is updated.<br />
* Fixed iPad layout issues on iOS 9.x.<br />
* Attempt at fixing sporadic crash on ad interstitial dismiss.<br />
    ]]></change>
	</changes>
	<changes>
		<version>7.5.0</version>
		<change><![CDATA[
Features:<br />
+ Full iOS 9 compatibility.<br />
+ New, modern cleanup user interface.<br />
+ Added battery usage data cleanup step.<br />
+ Added automatic dependency management to the Cydia Substrate addon tool.<br />
+ Added full theming support via WinterBoard and Anemone. See the theming documentation.<br />
* Re-enabling a Cydia Substrate addon or Preference Bundle prior to uninstalling it via Cydia is not necessary anymore.<br />
* The images removal tools now support the iPhone 6s, 6s plus, iPad mini 4 and 6th gen iPod touch.<br />
* The preference files tool now attempts to indicate which tweak each file belongs to.<br />
* The wallpapers tool can now remove live wallpapers.<br />
    ]]></change>
		<change><![CDATA[
Fixes and improvements:<br />
* Fixed bug where the Cydia Substrate addons tools would fail to recognize a symlink to a dylib, when both were placed in the DynamicLibraries directory.<br />
* Fixed bug that prevented the Preference Bundles tool to appropriately get the icon for packages with multiple bundles.<br />
* Fixed bug that disallowed the log file from being written while the device was locked with a passcode.<br />
* Potentially fixed bug that could cause iCleaner to crash when dependencies were not respected while disabling tweaks.<br />
* Reduced iCleanerLib memory footprint.<br />
* Improved iCleanerLib loading and initialization.<br />
* Added device identifiers usage consent alert for european users to comply with EU privacy directives.<br />
* The log file is now automatically loaded completely once the text view is scrolled to the bottom.
* User interface improvements.<br />
* Miscellaneous performance improvements.<br />
    ]]></change>
	</changes>
</changelog>
