<package>
	<id>apktw.me.alfhaily.cercube</id>
	<name>Cercube 3 (iOS 7/8/9)</name>
	<version>1.1.9</version>
	<compatibility>
		<firmware>
			<miniOS>7.0</miniOS>
		</firmware>
	</compatibility>
	<dependencies>
		<package>firmware (>= 7.0)</package>
		<package>mobilesubstrate</package>
		<package>com.rpetrich.rocketbootstrap</package>
		<package>com.ouraigua.jodebox</package>
	</dependencies>
	<descriptionlist>
		<description><![CDATA[
Compatible with iOS 7, 8 and 9<br />
<br />
Cercube 3 is the best all-in-one video download extension for the YouTube app.<br />
This is an extension for the official YouTube app which can be downloaded from the AppStore for free.<br />
<br />
The official YouTube app is a great YouTube client but it lacks a several key features that most YouTube users want: Video downloads, customizable playback quality, no ads and much more.<br />
<br />
Cercube 3 takes care of the missing features in YouTube app.<br />
<br />
It’s build right into the YouTube app and adds these great features to the app:<br />
• Download any video in any available quality. (from 144p to 1080p).<br />
• View, manage and share all your downloads in Cercube’s download manager.<br />
• Import downloaded songs and videos to your Music Library, or Videos app.<br />
• Block all promoted cells and video ads.<br />
• Send downloaded videos via AirDrop to other devices.<br />
• Background playback capability for both streamed and downloaded videos.<br />
• Downloaded videos are displayed within a beautifully crafted downloads manager that shows all the available information.<br />
• Select which page to display when launching the YouTube app.<br />
• Unique short-hold button gestures.<br />
• HD streaming on mobile networks.<br />
• Auto replay videos.<br />
<br />
Cercube options are configurable from within the YouTube app settings.<br />
    ]]></description>
	</descriptionlist>
	<screenshots>
		<screenshot>
			<description></description>
			<image>apktw.me.alfhaily.cercube_1.jpg</image>
		</screenshot>		
		<screenshot>
			<description></description>
			<image>apktw.me.alfhaily.cercube_2.jpg</image>
		</screenshot>		
		<screenshot>
			<description></description>
			<image>apktw.me.alfhaily.cercube_3.jpg</image>
		</screenshot>		
		<screenshot>
			<description></description>
			<image>apktw.me.alfhaily.cercube_4.jpg</image>
		</screenshot>		
		<screenshot>
			<description></description>
			<image>apktw.me.alfhaily.cercube_5.jpg</image>
		</screenshot>		
    <screenshot>
			<description></description>
			<image>apktw.me.alfhaily.cercube_6.jpg</image>
		</screenshot>		
	</screenshots>
	<changelog>
		<change>New redesigned player for audio downloads.</change>
    <change>Bug fixes and improvements.</change>
	</changelog>
	<links>
		<link>
			<name>APK.TW 台灣中文網</name>
			<url>http://apk.tw/</url>
		</link>
	</links>
</package>