<package>
	<id>apktw.org.thebigboss.dissident</id>
	<name>Dissident</name>
  <name>（已破解DRM）</name>
	<version>1.4-3</version>
	<compatibility>
		<firmware>
			<miniOS>8.0</miniOS>
		</firmware>
	</compatibility>
	<dependencies>
		<package>firmware (>= 8.0)</package>
		<package>mobilesubstrate</package>
		<package>applist</package>
	</dependencies>
	<descriptionlist>
		<description><![CDATA[
Compatible with iOS 8 and 9.<br />
<br />
Dissident finally brings true application background management back to your device.<br />
<br />
Dissident features five background modes which you can assign either globally or to individual applications:<br />
<br />
- Off (Disables backgrounding)<br />
- Fast Freeze (Instantly suspend apps in memory)<br />
- Native (Apple's way)<br />
- Unlimited native (Infinite background tasks)<br />
- Foreground (iOS behaves as if the app was running in front)<br />
<br />
Some other features are:<br />
- Prevent termination (Prevents iOS from closing apps)<br />
- Force automatic launch (Launch apps on respring/reboot)<br />
- Force automatic relaunch (Relaunch apps when they close)<br />
<br />
- Icon badges to see which app is running, and in which mode<br />
- Statusbar icons to display the background mode of the currently openen app<br />
- Activator actions to toggle baackgrounding modes on the fly<br />
<br />
If you don't use Activator or libstatusbar, no problem. Dissident doesn't depend on these two tweaks, but if installed, you can use their features.<br />
<br />
Dissident adds a settings app to the homescreen.<br />
<br />
Follow @biscoditch on Twitter for updates and stuff.<br />
    ]]></description>
	</descriptionlist>
	<screenshots>
		<screenshot>
			<description></description>
			<image>apktw.org.thebigboss.dissident_1.jpg</image>
		</screenshot>
		<screenshot>
			<description></description>
			<image>apktw.org.thebigboss.dissident_2.jpg</image>
		</screenshot>
		<screenshot>
			<description></description>
			<image>apktw.org.thebigboss.dissident_3.jpg</image>
		</screenshot>
		<screenshot>
			<description></description>
			<image>apktw.org.thebigboss.dissident_4.jpg</image>
		</screenshot>
	</screenshots>
	<changelog>
		<change>Fixed app layout on iPad</change>
    <change>Minor bug fixes</change>
    <change>App Store now kills Apps when updated</change>
    <change>Removed the Toggle Foregrounding Permanent activator action</change>
    <change>Changed the way of displaying the icon badge, Dissident now uses the update badge</change>
    <change>Changed the way of forced launch and forced relaunch (Dissident doesn't use temporary foregrounding to update the UI anymore)</change>
    <change>Fixed statusbar not showing until app is opened</change>
    <change>Fixed icon badge not displaying the correct background mode (happened when toggling foregrounding with activator)</change>
    <change>Fixed statusbar not displaying the correct background mode (happened when toggling foregrounding with activator)</change>
    <change>Support for iOS 9</change>
	</changelog>
	<links>
		<link>
			<name>APK.TW 台灣中文網</name>
			<url>http://apk.tw/</url>
		</link>
	</links>
</package>